var questions = [
    {
        question:"In which of the following continent the Andes Mountain Range is located?",
        answers:['Australia',"Europe","S. America","N. America"],
        correctAnswer: "S. America"
    },
    {
        question:"The largest mountain series of the world?",
        answers:['Himalaya',"Andes","Rockies","Alps"],
        correctAnswer: "Andes"
    },
    {
        question:"Highest peaks of the world are mostly found in which type of mountains?",
        answers:["Old folded mountains","Young fold mountains", "Residual mountains", "Block mountains"],
        correctAnswer: "Young fold mountains"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is known as the 'Sea of mountains'?",
        answers:["Japan","British Columbia", "West coast of South America", "South East Asia"],
        correctAnswer: "British Columbia"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is the longest mountain range?",
        answers:["The Rocky","The Alps", "The Himalayas", "The Andes"],
        correctAnswer: "The Andes"
    },
    {
        question:"White Mountains are founded in?",
        answers:["Canada","Norway", "Russia", "USA"],
        correctAnswer: "USA"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following mountains is located in Germany?",
        answers:["Black Forest","Atlas", "Pyrenees", "Apennines"],
        correctAnswer: "Black Forest"
    },
    {
        question:"Black Mountain is situated in?",
        answers:["Canada","Norway", "Switzerland", "USA"],
        correctAnswer: "USA"
    },
    {
        question:"Drakensberg is a mountain of?",
        answers:["Botswana","Namibia", "South Africa", "Zambia"],
        correctAnswer: "South Africa"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following mountains is located in Italy?",
        answers:["Apennine","Pyrenees", "Dimaric Alps", "Zura"],
        correctAnswer: "Apennine"
    }
]